

CONTACT ME AT



wayne.thrower@hotmail.co.uk



Wayne Thrower



github.com/waynethrower

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTMI 5

CSS3

JavaScript (ES6)

React.js

Node.js

Express.js

PostgreSQL

Jest

Heroku

Netlify

Rest API

TOOLS

Postman

Figma

Slack

Visual Studio Code

GitHub

PERSONAL SKILLS

Continuous Learner

Communication

Active Team Player

Self Driven

Hard Worker

Adaptability

Organised

WAYNE THROWER

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Motivated ambitious Computer Science graduate, with over 2 years Software Development experience, my expertise includes software development, testing, programming and web design. I am a strong team player with an emphasis on providing quality technical work and technically sound solutions in a timely manner with minimal supervision.

School of Code has enabled me to learn the latest Full Stack technologies such as JavaScript (ES6) and React on the front end plus Node.js, Express.js, Rest API and PostgreSQL for the back end whilst refreshing AGILE methodologies on Real World projects.

1 Week Project

React.js, Node, Express, PostgreSQL

In a team of 4, we were given a week to create a solution to improving the lives of bootcampers. We created Code Buddy to support bootcampers with posting code problems in a structured way.

Final Project

Autho, Next.js, React.js, Node, Express, PostgreSQL

In a team of 6, we had 4 weeks to come up with a solution to a problem of our choice. We decided on a Cookbook that you could store more than just recipes, it would be a family recipe cookbook to share family recipes.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Graduate Software Developer

Cooper Research Technology | Aug 2018 - Sept 2021

- Worked in a Cross-discipline team on group projects putting communication with team members at the heart of every project
- Individually on smaller software projects
- Creating functional and technical applications that met industry standards
- Working to deadlines, meeting timescales allowing time for thorough testing
- Ensured documentation was updated ready for launch

Retail Manager

Tesco | April 1997 - Nov 2016

- Managed different departments & different size teams
- Communicating with other members of the management team
- Managing budgets & creating active plans to meet and surpass key KPI's

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

University of Nottingham

BSc Computer Science 2:1 | Sept 2014- Aug 2018

- Project planning, coordination, and Ethics
- Languages: C, C#, C++, Java, Haskell & OpenGL
- Programming Paradigms: OOP, Functional, Procedural & Modular
- AGILE Software Engineering Principles & Methodologies
- Group & Individual Projects